{
  "id": "030-weather",
  "title": "Weather & Plans",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "oras",
      "choices": [
        "weather",
        "wind",
        "rain",
        "sun"
      ],
      "answer": "weather",
      "tts": "oras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "lietus",
      "choices": [
        "rain",
        "snow",
        "sun",
        "wind"
      ],
      "answer": "rain",
      "tts": "lietus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "saulė",
      "choices": [
        "sun",
        "rain",
        "cloud",
        "wind"
      ],
      "answer": "sun",
      "tts": "saulė"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "šalta",
      "choices": [
        "cold",
        "hot",
        "warm",
        "cool"
      ],
      "answer": "cold",
      "tts": "šalta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "karšta",
      "choices": [
        "hot",
        "cold",
        "warm",
        "cool"
      ],
      "answer": "hot",
      "tts": "karšta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "oras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "lietus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "saulė"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "šalta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "karšta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "oras",
      "choices": [
        "weather",
        "wind",
        "rain",
        "sun"
      ],
      "answer": "weather",
      "tts": "oras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "lietus",
      "choices": [
        "rain",
        "snow",
        "sun",
        "wind"
      ],
      "answer": "rain",
      "tts": "lietus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "saulė",
      "choices": [
        "sun",
        "rain",
        "cloud",
        "wind"
      ],
      "answer": "sun",
      "tts": "saulė"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "šalta",
      "choices": [
        "cold",
        "hot",
        "warm",
        "cool"
      ],
      "answer": "cold",
      "tts": "šalta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "karšta",
      "choices": [
        "hot",
        "cold",
        "warm",
        "cool"
      ],
      "answer": "hot",
      "tts": "karšta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "oras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "lietus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "saulė"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "šalta"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "karšta"
    }
  ]
}